<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><atom:link href="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><title>RSS-Feed Digital Guide</title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/]]></link><description><![CDATA[Our guidebook's take on topics relating to servers, websites, hosting, domains, online marketing, and e-mails is suitable for both web hosting beginners and server experts.]]></description><copyright><![CDATA[IONOS]]></copyright><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><lastBuildDate><![CDATA[Mon, 31 Mar 2025 08:03:22 +0000]]></lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[What is Armv9? AI-ready CPU architecture]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/know-how/armv9/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/know-how/armv9/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/cpu-t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>Armv9 represents a significant leap forward in the evolution of ARM architectures, offering major improvements in security, computing power and efficiency. Discover everything about the innovations of Armv9 and why it excels when used for dedicated servers, AI and ML, and mobile and embedded systems.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 07:04:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the most secure cloud storage? 4 secure clouds to consider]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/tools/most-secure-cloud-storage/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/tools/most-secure-cloud-storage/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/sicherste-cloud_t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>If you like to store your data in the cloud, you’ve probably wondered which cloud storage is the most secure. In order to assess the security of a cloud service, various factors such as the server location or the data encryption must be considered. We show you which security deficits can occur and present the best encrypted cloud storage.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 12:04:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are ARM servers?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/know-how/arm-server/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/know-how/arm-server/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/blade-server-t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>The characteristics and architecture of ARM servers open up new possibilities. With their potential to reduce operating costs and improve environmental impact, they are an attractive option for companies seeking a future-proof server architecture. Learn how ARM-based servers work and which use cases they are best suited for.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 10:04:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Adding a mailbox to Outlook: How to set up access to mailboxes in Outlook]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/e-mail/technical-matters/add-mailbox-to-outlook/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/e-mail/technical-matters/add-mailbox-to-outlook/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/postfach-hinzufuegen.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>Microsoft Outlook has a feature that allows you to manage mailboxes in one client. To do this, the manager of a mailbox only has to share it. These selected users can then add the mailbox to their Outlook account to help the mailbox owner process incoming and outgoing mail traffic. Depending on the access given, multiple users may have the power to do a lot of work via e-mail, relaxing the workload. Find out how in this guide.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 09:04:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is an ARM processor and how does the architecture work?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/know-how/arm-processor-architecture/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/know-how/arm-processor-architecture/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/cpu-t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>ARM processors are on the rise. Since the introduction of 64-bit ARM processor architectures, ARM chips have become highly attractive for server applications. The combination of energy efficiency, flexibility and performance not only reduces costs but also excels in fields like artificial intelligence. Find out more here.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 08:04:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Which WordPress shop plugin is the best? 6 options compared]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/hosting/blogs/wordpress-shop-plugins/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/hosting/blogs/wordpress-shop-plugins/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/online-shop-performance-t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>WordPress shop plugins add all essential features needed to develop and operate an online store to the popular content management system. The best option depends largely on the size and scope of your planned ecommerce project. Which WP ecommerce plugins are worth a closer look? And what exactly distinguishes them from standalone shop systems?]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 07:04:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are the best cloud providers in Germany?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/tools/cloud-in-germany/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/server/tools/cloud-in-germany/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/deutsche-cloud-anbieter_t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>Cloud storage providers like Google Drive or OneDrive are extremely popular, but their data protection standards are relatively low compared to providers based in Europe. If you are looking for high level of data protection, a cloud based in Germany is a great option. Find out everything you need to know about using cloud storage in Germany and which German cloud storage providers offer their services in the U.S.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 14:04:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is artificial intelligence (AI)?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/online-marketing/online-sales/what-is-artificial-intelligence/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/online-marketing/online-sales/what-is-artificial-intelligence/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/ki-t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>AI is one of the most exciting technologies out there and will continue to be in the coming years. Already, it’s being used in various applications, transforming both our personal and professional lives. But what exactly is artificial intelligence? We’ll take a look at different definitions of AI, how AI works and what the advantages and disadvantages of this technology are.]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 06:04:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is semi-supervised learning?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/online-marketing/search-engine-marketing/semi-supervised-learning/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/online-marketing/search-engine-marketing/semi-supervised-learning/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/DigitalGuide/Teaser/machine-learning-t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>Semi-supervised learning blends the strengths of supervised and unsupervised learning, allowing models to train efficiently using a small number of labeled data points alongside a larger set of unlabeled data. This approach taps into the potential of unused data, making machine learning models more powerful. Discover how this process works and where it can have the greatest impact.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 15:04:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are decision support systems?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/websites/web-development/decision-support-system/]]></link><guid><![CDATA[https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/websites/web-development/decision-support-system/]]></guid><description><![CDATA[<img src="https://www.ionos.com/digitalguide/fileadmin/StartupGuide/Teaser/drupal-vs-wp-t.jpg" width="1200" height="630" alt="" /><br/>Decision support systems (DSS) help managers and specialists make well-founded decisions about operational and strategic tasks. They support decision processes by consolidating and illustrating relevant data. In this article, we explain how decision support systems work, what they’re used for and what advantages they bring.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 13:04:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
<!-- Thursday 10, April 2025 18:13:30 -->